9-11heroes.us 2013-03-10

# Privacy Policy

|  | 

* * *

_Submit Your  
9-11 Memorial:_

 * [For victims at  
    Pentagon & flights](http://www.9-11heroes.us/victims-flight-pentagon.php "Leave memorial thoughts for 9-11 victims of Pentagon and flights.")

 * [Leave generic  
    9-11 memorials](http://www.9-11heroes.us/memorial-thoughts.php "Leave general memorial thoughts about 9-11")

* * *

_Songs and poems:_

* * *

* * *

_About kids:_

* * *

 * [Asbestos exposure  
    at Ground Zero](http://www.9-11heroes.us/asbestos.php)

* * *

Fly Your Own American Flag: [](http://www.amazon.com/Annin-Tough-Tex-Woven-Polyester-Replacement/dp/B003J36E50/)

* * *

* * *

| 

> Education on visitor privacy is important to us here. 
> 
> We recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. This article will inform you about the various types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit http://9-11heroes.us, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell or otherwise your personal information to third parties. 
> 
> ## Use of Log Files
> 
> As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the type of browser you used to visit our site (such as Google Chrome, Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox), the time at which you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 
> 
> ## Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
> 
> We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 
> 
> We also use third party advertising services to display advertisements, such as Google through the Google AdSense program. Some or all of those advertising services may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will send these advertisers information about your visit including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes. Geo-targeting is sometimes used for the purposes of matching advertisements with visitors based on certain attributes that visitor has. An example of this type of geo-targeting would be showing Idaho movie theatre ads to someone located in Idaho, or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited, such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites. 
> 
> ## DoubleClick DART cookies
> 
> We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google.s DoubleClick service, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (.interest based targeting.). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Miami, you may see Miami hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses .non personally identifiable information.. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 
> 
> You may choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 
> 
> Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 
> 
> If you submit your email when contacting us via the [contact form on this page](http://www.9-11heroes.us/contact.php), we may use your email address to contact you. We are not storing email addresses submitted via that contact form, nor do we ever give or sell your email address to any third party. HOWEVER, if you do put your email address into a memorial comment, those addresses may end up published online.  
>  We try to keep advertisements to a minimum on this website and we don't have long term sponsors. The revenue from the advertisements goes towards the costs of maintaining this site. From time to time we may post an affiliate link to a product related to our site, and we will receive a small commission if you purchase through such links. 
> 
> Questions? Contact us.

---|---|---
